Guide to the Stanford University, Information Technology Services, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1985-104
  - Completed Projects 10/31/1981 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - OFG (Operations & Finance Group) 2/9/1982 - 2/23/1982 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Printed Messages 12/17/1981 - 3/15/1982 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - OFG Meeting Notes 12/16/1981 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Management Calendar 1/20/1982 - 8/31/1982 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - MAG Agenda 1/22/1982 - 2/16/1982 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - MAG Meeting 11/17/1981 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Mike M. Roberts: Correspondence 1/1980 – 12/1980 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Vice Presidents Group Meeting 2/23/1982 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Visiting Committee Meeting 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Space Planning 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Trips 4/30/1980 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - OFG Minutes, Agenda, Background 1981 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Organizational Charts 9/1977 - 2/1980 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - RLIN Performance Problems Report 3/1982 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Department of Medicine Office Systems Review (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Budget Schedule 11/10/1980 - 12/8/1980 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Merit Computer Network 6/12/1981 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Visitors 1981 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Mike M. Roberts IBM Talk 4/20/1981 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - CICS Evaluation 9/1/1981 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - List of Cost Centers 1/18/1982 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - RLG Annual Report 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Western Educational Computer Conference 11/12/1981 - 11/13/1981 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - ARL Meeting 2/1-5/1981 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - EDUCOM Conference 11/8-10/1982 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Seminar on Academic Computing 8/1982 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - EDUCOM Strategic Planning Seminar 1/14/1983 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - American Bell 5/5/1983 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - CAUSE Strategic Planning Council 12/12/1983 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - New Technologies Class Lecture 7/12/1983 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Organizational Charts: Computers at Stanford 12/1981 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Organizational Charts: CIT Staff Categories (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Organizational Charts: CIT Consolidated Budget 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Organizational Charts: CIT Node Budget 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Organizational Charts: Information Function: University Perspective “The Matrix” (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Organizational Charts: Information Function: Staff Activities (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Organizational Charts: Information Function: Line Activities (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Organizational Charts: Computer Systems and Services (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Organizational Charts: Graphic Work 2/1982 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Organizational Charts: CIT Ancillary Services 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Organizational Charts: CIT Budget, Fiscal year 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Organizational Charts: CIT Program and Product Development 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Organizational Charts: CIT Management Expense 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Organizational Charts: CIT, A Brief History 1967-1980 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Organizational Charts: Guide to Computer and Technical Resources - Illustrations 1981 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Organizational Charts: The Information Function: University Perspective (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Organizational Charts: Future of Computing Task Force: Outline of Contrast (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Organizational Charts: Future of Computing Task Force: Prospective View (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Organizational Charts: Future of Computing Task Force: Preface (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Organizational Charts: Self Study Group 1982 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Organizational Charts: EDUCOM Strategic Planning Meeting 6/14/1983 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence Logs 1981 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence Logs 1982 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence Logs 6/2/1980 - 1/30/1981 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence Logs 10/1/1982 - 8/31/1983 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Planning Retreat 10/21/1982 - 10/22/1982 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Confidential items removed from: Personnel 8/19/1980 - 12/6/1982 (accession ARCH-1985-104, box 15, folder 30 (Box Restricted 1)
  - Confidential items removed from: Personnel: ITS memos 1981-1983 (accession ARCH-1985-104, Box 15, folder 34) (Box Restricted 1)
  - Confidential items removed from: SCIP: Salaries and Selections 1977-78 (accession ARCH-1985-104, box 23, folder 14) (Box Restricted 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1999-102
  - Stanford University computer inventory 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Lisp 1.6 Manual by Lynn H. Quam and Whitfield Diffle (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - LOTS FORTRAN Reference Manual, April 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - FORTRAN Development Newsletter 1975-81 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - LOTS DECsystem-20 Overview. LOTS Operating Note 1, Revision 5; 25 September 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - PASCAL at LOTS by Armando R. Rodriguez, September 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Computer Printout: Manual of the XPOP Programming System. Electronic Sciences Laboratory, Lockheed Missiles and Space Company, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - SPIRES Master List of SCIP and CSD Programs 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2009-195
  - Using FORTRAN Language Processors, April 1981 (Box 1)
  - FORmula TRANslation. Stanford Computation Center, October, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Fortran Coding Form (pad of empty forms) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Reference cards: orvyl/370 command language 1975; HASP statement reference 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2010-033
  - Stanford University Computation Center Users Manual. Appendices B-E, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Computing Services User's Manual Fourth Edition, Sections 1-3, May 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Computing Services User's Manual Fourth Edition, Sections 4-Index, May 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)